Finding Aid for the Livingston Gearhart Collection of Scores, 1930-1996
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Arrangements, transcriptions, and editions of works by other named composers, 1930-2009, II; Folder 115-228
  - Brubeck, Dave Nomad; arranged Nomad: orchestration [196-], 1 ms. score (14 p.); 34 cm. + 21 ms. parts; 28 cm.; Originally for clarinet, trombone, and bass; arranged for orchestra. Cover title. Holograph score (Pencil); Photocopied parts reproduced from holograph. Accompanied by 1 score (only 1 page partially completed) with unfinished changes for revision; 1 color photocopy of score (14 p.); 1 letter from Dave Brubeck to Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf); 2 notes from Pamela Gearhart (1 on envelope; 1 leaf each). (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Brubeck, Dave Ostinato; arranged Ostinato [196-], 1 ms. score ([18] p.); 49 cm.; Arranged for orchestra. Caption title. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 note presumably from Livingston Gearhart (1 leaf); 1 index card from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Brubeck, Dave Watusi drums; arranged Watusi drums 1966, 1 score (24 p.); 28 cm. + 2 condensed scores (8 p. each); 18-28 cm. + 58 parts; 28 cm.; Cover title. Duration: ca. 3:00. Accompanied by 1 note from Dave Brubeck to Livingston Gearhart dated Sept. 2, 1965 (1 leaf). Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania, Shawnee Press (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Chausson, Ernest, 1855-1899. Poème, violin, orchestra; arranged Poème [1989], 1 ms. score (26 p.); 31-32 cm.; Originally for violin and orchestra; arranged for violin and piano. Cover title. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 letter from Fritz Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Chausson, Ernest, 1855-1899. Poème, violin, orchestra; arranged Poème for violin and piano 2009, 1 score (26 p.); 28 cm.; Originally for violin and orchestra; arranged for violin and piano. Cover title. "The piano reduction was written by Livingston Gearhart in 1989"--Notes on cover verso. [United States]: Anyares Pub. (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Christy, Edwin Pearce, 1815-1862. Good night, ladies; arranged Good night, ladies: for SAB with four-hand piano accompaniment 1964, 1 score (7 p.); 27 cm.; Alternate title: Farewell ladies. Caption title. Words and melody by Edwin Pearce Christy, also know by the title Farewell ladies. Duration: ca. 2:15. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - De Curtis, Ernesto, 1875-1937. Torna a Surriento; arranged Come back to Sorrento? [between 1976 and 1996], 1 ms. score ([3] p.); 35 cm.; For alto, tenor, and baritone saxophones. Caption title. "Not sure"--Caption. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Dances, piano; arranged Danse: orchestration [196-], 1 ms. score (44 p.); 35 cm. + 28 ms. parts; 31-33 cm.; Originally for piano; arranged for orchestra. Cover title. "For U.B. orch. -- late 60's (we had good French horns!). Used for Ithaca College -- 1975? Used for Community Music School orch -- 60s"--Accompanying leaf. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph (Pencil), additional annotations in red and blue pencil. Includes 4 ms. leaves of revisions dated 1976. (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Mandoline; arranged Mandoline [between 1960 and 1980?], 1 ms. score (14 p.); 32 cm.; Originally for voice and piano; arranged for low voice and string orchestra. Cover title. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 typewritten note (1 leaf) presumably from Livingston Gearhart. Score lacks words; presumably meant to be sung in French. (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Preludes, piano, book 1. Fille aux cheveux de lin; arranged La fille aux cheveux du lin [between 1977 and 1978], 1 ms. score ([4] p.) + 7 ms. parts; 32 cm.; Originally for solo piano; arranged for solo violin with string orchestra accompaniment. Caption title. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Delius, Frederick, 1862-1934. Brigg Fair; arranged Brigg fair: for two pianos, four hands [between 1940 and 1960?], 1 ms. score ([4] p.); 34 cm.; Originally for orchestra. Title supplied by cataloger. Arrangement is unfinished. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Farnaby, Giles, ca. 1565-1640. For two virginals For 2 virginals [between 1935 and 1940], 1 ms. score ([1] leaf); 34 cm.; For two pianos. Caption title. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Fattorini, Gabriele Ricercare del nono tono Ricercar [between 1976 and 1996], 1 ms. score ([1] leaf); 35 cm.; Transcribed for SATT saxophones. Caption title. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Pavan, orchestra, op. 50, F♯ minor; arranged Pavane, op. 50 [between 1960 and 1972], 1 ms. score ([16] p.); 32 cm.; Originally for chorus and orchestra; arranged for orchestra. Caption title. Reproduced from holograph. Accompanied by 1 typescript (1 leaf) of technical information from Livingston Gearhart; 1 analysis of the work (1 leaf) by Livingston Gearhart. (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Pavan, orchestra, op. 50, F♯ minor; arranged Pavane 1972, 1 score (20 p.) + 50 parts; 29 cm.; Cover title. Arrangement simplified for youth orchestra. Arrangement supplied for the Community Music School Orchestra, Buffalo, N.Y. Includes note on the transcription by the publisher. Duration: ca. 6:00. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Pavan, orchestra, op. 50, F♯ minor; arranged Pavane 1972, 1 condensed score (8 p.); 17 cm.; Cover title. Arrangement simplified for youth orchestra. Arrangement supplied for the Community Music School Orchestra, Buffalo, N.Y. Includes note on the transcription by the publisher. Duration: ca. 6:00. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Pièces brèves. Adagietto; arranged Elegie, op. 84 [1972], 1 ms. score ([5] p.) + 2 ms. parts; 32 cm.; Originally for piano; arranged for string orchestra. Cover title. Parts for violoncello and bass only. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph (Pencil); Bass part reproduced from holograph. Accompanied by 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Ferling, Franz Wilhelm, 1796-1874. Etudes, oboe, op. 31. Selections; arranged Four etudes for oboe and piano [between 1995 and 1996], 4 ms. scores; 35 cm.; Originally for solo oboe; arranged for oboe with piano accompaniment. Includes #1, #5, #13, and #27. Title supplied by cataloger. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 3 photocopied letters (1 leaf each) from John de Lancie; 1 photocopied note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf); 1 photocopy of Ferling's published score (3 leaves); 1 photocopied note from Livingston Gearhart (1 leaf); 1 photocopied score of Etude #1 with annotations (3 leaves). (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Fischer, Johann, 1646-1716 or 17. Tafel-Musik. No. 14; arranged Antiques refinished: Marche [1978], 5 ms. parts; 32 cm.; Alternate title: Antiques refinished for wind quartet [i.e. quintet]. Alternate title: Refinished antique. Alternate title: Marche. Originally for 4 unspecified instruments, possibly a combination of strings and winds; arranged for oboe, English horn, horn, and 2 bassoons. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Manuscript (Ink). (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - Fischer, Johann, 1646-1716 or 17. Tafel-Musik. No. 14; arranged March: an antique refinished [1978], 1 ms. score ([8] p.) + 4 ms. parts; 32 cm.; Alternate title: Antiques refinished for brass quartet. Alternate title: Antique refinished. Alternate title: Caption subtitle on parts: Refinished antique. Originally for 4 unspecified instruments, possibly a combination of strings and winds; arranged for two trumpets, horn, and trombone. Caption title. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Date in caption on trumpet parts: 1978. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by: [4] p. of manuscript sketches (27 cm.). (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - Fischer, Johann, 1646-1716 or 17. Tafel-Musik. No. 14; arranged March: an antique refinished 1998, 1 score (5 p.) + 4 parts; 27 cm.; Alternate title: Antique refinished. Originally for 4 unspecified instruments, possibly a combination of strings and winds; arranged for 2 trumpets, horn, and trombone. Duration: ca. 2:00. Delaware Water Gap, PA: Concert Works Unlimited (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Goodale, Walter S Alma mater song; arranged U.B. alma mater [1964?], 1 ms. score (5 p.); 35 cm.; Alternate title: University at Buffalo alma mater. Arranged for wind ensemble. Cover title. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Ave Maria (Vocal version); arranged And a little child shall lead them: Ave maria: for a small pianist, with chorus SATB [between 1950 and 1970], 1 ms. score (6 leaves); 32 cm.; Alternate title: Ave maria. For solo piano with SATB accompaniment. Caption title. Gounod's work based on J.S. Bach's Prelude no. 1 from the first book of the Well-Tempered Clavier. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 typescript note (1 leaf) from Livingston Gearhart about the piece. Latin words. (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Grean, Charles R Thing; arranged The thing 1960, 1 score (12 p.); 27 cm.; Alternate title: First line of text: While I was walking down the beach. For SATB chorus with piano accompaniment. Cover title. Includes tone syllables to be used as a choral enunciation aid. Duration: ca. 2:30. Performance note on p. [2] of cover. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - Harrison, Annie Fortescue, 1851-1944. In the gloaming; arranged In the gloaming [between 1950 and 1970], 1 ms. score ([2] p.); 32 cm.; For TTBB chorus, unaccompanied. Caption title. Words by Meta Orred. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Schöpfung. Himmel erzählen die Ehre Gottes. English; arranged The spacious firmament 1965, 1 score (11 p.); 27 cm.; For SATB chorus with piano or organ. Caption title. Duration: ca. 4:00. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - Holst, Gustav, 1874-1934. Double concerto. Variations on a ground; arranged Variations over a ground [between 1960 and 1970], 1 ms. score (20 leaves); 22-35 cm.; Arranged for orchestra. Cover title. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Reproduced from holograph. Accompanied by 2 notes (1 leaf each) from Livingston Gearhart about the piece; 1 photocopied newspaper clipping from the Buffalo Evening News dated Dec. 12, 1970 (1 leaf); 1 concert program (1 leaf) titled Grounds for diversity dated Dec. 10, 1970. (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Johnson, J. Rosamond (John Rosamond), 1873-1954. Dry bones; arranged Dry bones [between 1940 and 1950?], 2 ms. parts; 31 cm.; Traditional song with music adapted by J. Rosamond Johnson. Piano parts to accompany the published SATB chorus version. Caption title. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by [1] leaf of ms. sketches (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Johnson, J. Rosamond (John Rosamond), 1873-1954. Dry bones; arranged Dry bones: 2nd piano: TTBB [between 1940 and 1950?], [2] leaves of ms. music; 31 cm.; Traditional song with music adapted by J. Rosamond Johnson. 2nd piano part arranged to accompany the published TTBB chorus version. Caption title. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Johnson, J. Rosamond (John Rosamond), 1873-1954. Dry bones; arranged Dry bones: a rhythmic spiritual: for men's glee club [c1946], 1 score (19 p.); 27 cm.; Traditional song with music adapted by J. Rosamond Johnson. For chorus (TTBB), double bass (ad.lib.), percussion and piano. "Based upon the version of the Delta Rhythm Boys." "A Fred Waring arrangement." New York: Shawnee Press (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Johnson, J. Rosamond (John Rosamond), 1873-1954. Dry bones; arranged Dry bones: a rhythmic spiritual: for mixed voices [l946], 1 score (19 p.); 27 cm.; Traditional song with music adapted by J. Rosamond Johnson. Cover title. For chorus (SATB), string bass (ad. lib.), percussion and piano. "Based upon the version of the Delta Rhythm Boys." "A Fred Waring arrangement." Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - Johnson, J. Rosamond (John Rosamond), 1873-1954. Dry bones; arranged Dry bones: SAB with piano accompaniment 1960, 1 score (19 p.); 27 cm.; Traditional song with music adapted by J. Rosamond Johnson. Caption title. Includes optional percussion parts. Duration: ca. 2:30. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - Johnson, J. Rosamond (John Rosamond), 1873-1954. Dry bones; arranged English and Japanese Dry bones 1946, 1 score (39 p.); 26 cm.; Traditional song with music adapted by J. Rosamond Johnson. For chorus (TTBB), double bass (ad.lib.), percussion and piano. Score presented twice: once in F major, once in B♭ major. Performances notes precede score. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press; Tokyo: Toa Music English and Japanese words. (Box 9, Folder 175)
  - Joplin, Scott, 1868-1917. Pine apple rag; arranged ½ of Pine apple rag is enough? [between 1976 and 1996], 1 ms. score ([2] p.); 35 cm. + 4 ms. parts; 32 cm.; Alternate title: One half of Pine apple rag is enough. Alternate title: Pine apple rag. For AAT saxophones with optional baritone saxophone part. Caption title. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph score (Pencil); Manuscript parts (Pencil). (Box 9, Folder 176)
  - Keeney, Wendell, 1903- Mountain tune; arranged Mountain tune [between 1930 and 1936], 2 ms. parts; 32-35 cm.; Arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Caption title. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 photocopy of 1st piano part ([4] p.). (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - Keeney, Wendell, 1903- Mountain tune; arranged Mountain tune: two pianos, four-hands 1936, 2 scores (11 p. each); 31 cm.; New York: G. Schirmer (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - Lyadov, Anatoly Konstantinovich, 1855-1914. Russkie narodnye pesni, orchestra. Koliaa-Maleda; arranged Alleluia: anthem for Christmas or Easter: S.A.T.B. with piano accompaniment: from "Eight Russian folk songs" 1952, 1 score (8 p.); 27 cm.; Caption title. "Waring choir series". Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Lyadov, Anatoly Konstantinovich, 1855-1914. Russkie narodnye pesni, orchestra. Kolybelnaia; arranged Lullaby: from eight Russian folk songs for orchestra: for humming chorus, unaccompanied 1949, 1 score (4 p.); 27 cm.; For SATB chorus. Includes piano accompaniment for rehearsal only. Delaware Water Gap, Penna.: Shawnee Press (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - MacDowell, Edward, 1860-1908. Woodland sketches. To a wild rose; arranged To a hothouse rose [between 1945 and 1965], 1 ms. score (6 p.); 32 cm.; Arrangement of Edward MacDowell's piece for solo piano, To a wild rose. Possibly for two pianos, 4 hands, or SATB chorus with piano accompaniment. Optional additional instrumentation includes string bass and snare drum. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - Marais, Josef, 1905-1978. Sugarbush; arranged Sugarbush [between 1950 and 1970], 1 ms. score (3 leaves); 32 cm.; Alternate title: Sugarfoot. Alternate title: Honey burch. For women's chorus with piano accompaniment. Caption title. Source of the song is Marais's Songs from the veld: fourteen songs from South Africa. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Quartets, strings, no. 1, op. 12, E♭ major. Canzonetta; arranged Canzonetta [1973], 1 ms. score ([4] p.); 32 cm. + 8 ms. parts; 13-29 cm.; For string quartet with string orchestra accompaniment. Title from violin 1 part. Holograph score (Pencil); Holograph parts (Mimeograph). Accompanied by 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Quartets, strings, no. 1, op. 12, E♭ major. Canzonetta; arranged Canzonetta [1975], 1 ms. score ([4] p.); 34 cm. + 10 ms. parts; 2 cm.; For string quartet with string orchestra accompaniment. Caption title from score. "Revised 1975"--Caption. Holograph score (Pencil); Holograph parts (Mimeograph). Accompanied by 1 photocopied note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - Messiter, Arthur Henry, 1834-1916. Rejoice ye pure in heart; arranged Rejoice ye pure in heart [between 1950 and 1970?], 1 ms. score ([3] leaves); 32 cm.; Arranged for SSA chorus with piano accompaniment. Caption title. Music by Arthur H. Messiter; words by Edward H. Plumptre. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Madrigals, book 8. Lamento della ninfa Amor [between 1950 and 1970], 1 ms. score (7 p.); 32 cm.; Transcribed for women's chorus with piano accompaniment. Cover title. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 photocopied score ([6] p.) of Monteverdi's original madrigal. Italian words. (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Alleluja, K. 553 Alleluia: 4-part round [between 1950 and 1970], [1] leaf of ms. music; 32 cm.; Caption title. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 10, Folder 187)
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Don Giovanni. Madamina, il catalogo è questo; arranged Leporello [between 1940 and 1960], [7] p. of ms. music; 35 cm.; Orchestral accompaniment arranged for piano. Score does not contain voice part. Caption title. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 10, Folder 188)
  - Mussorgsky, Modest Petrovich, 1839-1881. Boris Godunov. Pesnia Varlaama; arranged The siege of Kazan [from] Boris [Godunov] [1938], 1 folder.; The siege of Kazan is arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Title from typescript note from Livingston Gearhart. "Piano version France 1938"--Accompanying note. Folder also includes 1 piano part from a 2 piano arrangement of the Coronation Scene from Act 1 (8 p.); 1 piano arrangement of the Change in Siege of Kazan ([1] leaf); 1 untitled sketch for 2 pianos ([3] leaves). Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf); 1 typescript note from Livingston Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 10, Folder 189)
  - Mysels, George, 1912- American is a very lucky man; arranged An American is a very lucky man: SATB with piano accompaniment 1958, 1 score (7 p.); 27 cm.; Alternate title: First line of text: As a citizen of the Forty-eight. Caption title. Duration: ca. 1:45. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 10, Folder 190)
  - Opera excerpts [198-], 1 ms. score (19 p.); 33-35 cm.; Arranged for string quartet. Excerpts include Der Vogelfänger bin ich ja (from The magic flute) by Mozart, Si mi chiamano mimi (from La bohème) by Puccini, Adagietto from L'Arlesienne suite no. 1 by Bizet, En fermant les yeux (from Manon) by Massenet, Overture to Forza del destino by Verdi, and Overture to The magic flute by Mozart. Title from accompanying note from Livingston Gearhart. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph (Photocopy). Accompanied by 2 letters (l leaf each) from Livingston Gearhart about the piece; 1 index card from Pamela Gearhart. (Box 10, Folder 191)
  - Pasquini, Bernardo, 1637-1710. Sonatas, harpsichords (2), H. 109, D minor Sonata a due cembali [between 1935 and 1945], 1 ms. score ([7] p.) + 1 ms. part; 32-34 cm.; For two pianos. Cover title from score. Part for second piano only. Holograph (Ink). (Box 10, Folder 192)
  - Porter, Cole, 1891-1964. Wake up and dream. What is this thing called love?; arranged Praeludium e fuga super "Was is das ding 'liebe' sogenante" [between 1976 and 1996], 1 ms. score ([4] leaves); 31 x 47 cm.; Alternate title: Was is das ding 'liebe' sogenante. Arranged for 6 unspecified instruments (2 sets of 3 instruments). Title from left margin of score. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 10, Folder 193)
  - Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Pesy, piano, op. 12. Marsh; arranged Marche, op. 12, #1 [between 1960 and 1980], 1 ms. score (10 p.); 35 cm.; Originally for piano; arranged for orchestra. Cover title. Performance notes precede score. Holograph (Pencil); emendations written in blue pencil. Score contains a conductor's performance markings in red pencil. (Box 10, Folder 194)
  - Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Pesy, piano, op. 12. Marsh; arranged Marche, op. 12, no. 1 1980, 2 scores (12 p. each) + 21 parts; 29 cm.; Originally for piano; arranged for orchestra. Cover title. Duration: ca. 1:50. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 10, Folder 195)
  - Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Pesy, piano, op. 12. Marsh; arranged Marche, op. 12, no. 1 1980, 1 condensed score (7 p.); 28 cm.; Cover title. Originally for piano. Duration: ca. 1:50. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 10, Folder 196)
  - Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Pesy, piano, op. 12. Marsh; arranged Marche, op. 12, no. 1 1930, 1 miniature score (7 p.); 19 cm.; Cover title. Originally for piano. Duration: ca. 1:50. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 10, Folder 197)
  - Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695. Under this stone; arranged Antiques refinished III: Round [between 1978 and 1996], 1 ms. score (2 leaves); 30 x 38 cm.; Alternate title: Antiques refinished 3. Originally for 3 voices or other treble instruments; arranged for flute, oboe, clarinet, violin, viola and cello. Caption title. Based on the 3-part round Under this stone by Henry Purcell. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph (Ink). Accompanied by: photocopy of score (22 x 28 cm.). (Box 10, Folder 198)
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Romansy, op. 34. Vocalise; arranged Vocalise [between 1951 and 1971], 1 ms. score (11 p.); 36 cm.; Originally for voice and piano; arranged for orchestra. Caption title. Holograph (Ozalid reproduction). Duration: 5:50 (without repeat); 8:00 (with repeat). (Box 10, Folder 199)
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Romansy, op. 34. Vocalise; arranged Vocalise, op. 34 1971, 1 score (12 p.) + 54 parts; 28 cm.; Originally for voice and piano; arranged for orchestra. Cover title. Duration: ca. 5:00. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 10, Folder 200)
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Suites, pianos (2), no. 1, op. 5 Slezy Tears: from opus 5 for two pianos 1948, 2 scores (12 p. each); 31 cm.; Caption title. New York: Shawnee Press (Box 10, Folder 201)
  - Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Ma mère l'oye (Piano duet). Pavane de la belle au bois dormant; arranged Pavane de la belle au bois dormant [between 1960 and 1980?], 1 ms. score ([1] leaf); 34 cm.; Originally for piano duet; arranged for orchestra. Arrangement is unfinished. Title supplied by cataloger. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 photocopied score ([3] p.) of Ravel's original orchestration. (Box 10, Folder 202)
  - Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Pavane pour une infante défunte; arranged Pavane [between 1960 and 1969], 1 ms. score ([12] p.) + 20 ms. parts; 32-35 cm.; Originally for piano; arranged for orchestra. Cover title from score. Holograph score (Pencil); manuscript parts (Ink and pencil). Emendations marked in blue pencil; conductor's performance markings in red pencil. Accompanied by 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 10, Folder 203)
  - Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Pavane pour une infante défunte; arranged Pavane: cello, string orch [1978 or 1979], 1 ms. score (4 p.) + 5 ms. parts; 32-35 cm.; Originally for piano; arranged for solo violoncello and string orchestra. Cover title from score. Holograph score (Pencil); Manuscript orchestral parts (Photocopy). Emendations marked in blue pencil. Accompanied by [2] p. of ms. sketches; 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 10, Folder 204)